







0543571806

Profile

Hello!

I am Cecile, I was born in Florida, USA but raised in Lima Peru.

I am 26 years old and I am a Clinical Psychologist who graduated from Pontificia Universidad Catolica del Peru (University). My interests include Text analysis, Sentiment analysis, Linguistics and Technology.

I consider myself to be independent, responsible, empathetic, and authentic.

Education

Humanities Studies, Pontificia Universidad Catolica del Peru

March 2014 — December 2015

Clinical Psychology, Pontificia Universidad Catolica del Peru

March 2016 — December 2019

Employment History

Summer School Assistant & Teacher, Club Hebraica, Lima-Peru

January 2013 — February 2019

Recreational activities for kids 2-6 years old

Childcare Nursery Practitioner, Rainbow, Tel Aviv

August 2020 — March 2021

Office Manager, Yeda Plus Uniprep, Tel Aviv

March 2021 — Present

Exam Proctor, IELTS & TOEFL English exam, Tel Aviv

March 2021 — Present

Manage communications between London International House and the office in Israel

Internships

Assistant psychologist, Public Mental Hospital "Victor Larco Herrera" 2019-2020, Lima-Peru

January 2019 — January 2020

Children and Adolescent's ambulatory ward (6 months)

Chronic elderly male patients ward (6 months)

References

References available upon request

Details

Tel Aviv Israel

0543571806

cblau@pucp.pe

Nationality

Peruvian

Skills

Communication Skills

Effective Time Management

Ability to Work Under

Pressure

Ability to Work in a Team

Customer Service

Fast Learner

Empathy

Flexibility and Adaptability

Computer Skills

IBM SPSS Statistics

Excel

Languages

Spanish

English

Hebrew